<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<errors type="step">

<error><code>err:XC0001</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the requested method is not supported.

    See: Serialization Options
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0002</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the value starts with the string --.

    See: Request Entity body conversion
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0003</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the requested auth-method isn't supported or the authentication challenge contains an authentication method that isn't supported.

    See: Specifying a request
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0004</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the status-only attribute has the value “true” and the detailed attribute does not have the value “true”.

    See: Specifying a request
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0005</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the request contains a c:body or c:multipart but the method does not allow for an entity body being sent with the request.

    See: Specifying a request
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0007</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the scheme of the URI reference is not supported.

    See: p:load
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0010</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the charset specified is not supported by the implementation or if charset is specified when encoding is not.

    See: p:unescape-markup
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0011</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the step is not allowed to retrieve from the specified location.

    See: p:load
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0012</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the contents of the directory path are not available to the step due to access restrictions in the environment in which the pipeline is run.

    See: p:directory-list
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0013</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the the pattern matches a processing instruction and the new name has a non-null namespace.

    See: p:rename
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0014</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the XML namespace (http://www.w3.org/XML/1998/namespace) or the XMLNS namespace (http://www.w3.org/2000/xmlns/) is the value of either the from option or the to option.

    See: p:namespace-rename
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0016</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the value supplied for any option specified for any step in this section is not of the type mandated in the step description, with phrases such as "The value of the some-name option must be a QName" or "the value of the some-flag option must be a boolean".

    See: Standard Step Library
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0017</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the absolute path does not identify a directory.

    See: p:directory-list
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0018</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the directory path's scheme is not supported.

    See: p:directory-list
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0019</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the documents are not equal, and the value of the fail-if-not-equal option is “true”.

    See: p:compare
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0020</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the value of a header specified via c:header (e.g. Content-Type) conflicts with the value for that header that the step and/or protocol implementation must set.

    See: Specifying a request
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0021</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the scheme of the href attribute is not supported.

    See: Specifying a request
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0022</code>
<description>

    it is a dynamic error if the content of the c:body element does not consist of exactly one element, optionally preceded and/or followed by any number of processing instructions, comments or whitespace characters

    See: Request Entity body conversion
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0023</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if a select expression or match pattern returns a node type that is not allowed by the step.

    See: Standard Step Library, p:add-attribute, p:insert, p:label-elements, p:make-absolute-uris, p:rename, p:replace, p:set-attributes, p:unwrap, p:wrap
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0025</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the match pattern matches the document element and the value of the position option is ”before” or ”after”.

    See: p:insert
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0026</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the document does not exist or is not well-formed.

    See: p:load
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0027</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the document is not valid or the step doesn't support DTD validation.

    See: p:load
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0028</code>
<description>

    it is a dynamic error if the content of the c:body element does not consist entirely of characters

    See: Request Entity body conversion
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0029</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if an XInclude error occurs during processing.

    See: p:xinclude
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0030</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the override-content-type value cannot be used (e.g. text/plain to override image/png).

    See: Managing the response
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0033</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the command cannot be run.

    See: p:exec
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0034</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the current working directory cannot be changed to the value of the cwd option.

    See: p:exec
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0035</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error to specify both result-is-xml and wrap-result-lines.

    See: p:exec
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0036</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the requested hash algorithm is not one that the processor understands or if the value or parameters are not appropriate for that algorithm.

    See: p:hash
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0037</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the value provided is not a properly x-www-form-urlencoded value.

    See: p:www-form-urldecode
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0038</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the specified version of XSLT is not available.

    See: p:xslt
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0039</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if a sequence of documents is provided to an XSLT 1.0 step.

    See: p:xslt
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0040</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the document element of the document that arrives on the source port is not c:request.

    See: p:http-request
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0041</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the match pattern matches any other kind of node.

    See: p:wrap
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0050</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the URI scheme is not supported or the step cannot store to the specified location.

    See: p:store
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0051</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the content-type specified is not supported by the implementation.

    See: p:unescape-markup
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0052</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the encoding specified is not supported by the implementation.

    See: Request Entity body conversion, p:unescape-markup
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0053</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the assert-valid option is true and the input document is not valid.

    See: p:validate-with-relax-ng, p:validate-with-xml-schema
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0054</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the assert-valid option is true and any Schematron assertions fail.

    See: p:validate-with-schematron
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0055</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the implementation does not support the specified mode.

    See: p:validate-with-xml-schema
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0056</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the specified initial mode or named template cannot be applied to the specified stylesheet.

    See: p:xslt
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0057</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the sequence that results from evaluating the XQuery contains items other than documents and elements.

    See: p:xquery
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0058</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the all and relative options are both “true”.

    See: p:add-xml-base
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0059</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the QName value in the attribute-name option uses the prefix 'xmlns' or any other prefix that resolves to the same namespace name as 'xmlns'.

    See: p:add-attribute
</description></error><error><code>err:XC0060</code>
<description>

    It is a dynamic error if the processor does not support the specified version of the UUID algorithm.

    See: p:uuid
</description>
</error>
    
</errors>

